campingroadtrip.com 2009-05-05

# Privacy Statement

Camping Road Trip, LLC ("Camping Road Trip") is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Camping Road Trip Web site, ("CampingRoadTrip.com") and governs data collection and usage. By using CampingRoadTrip.com, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

If you have any questions regarding this statement, please send an email to [administrator@campingroadtrip.com](mailto:administrator@campingroadtrip.com?Subject=Question%20regarding%20your%20Privacy%20Statement). This statement was last revised on March 1, 2009

Collection of your Personal Information

CampingRoadTrip.com collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name and birthday. CampingRoadTrip.com also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by CampingRoadTrip.com. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Camping Road Trip for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of CampingRoadTrip.com.

Third party Internet sites and services accessible through CampingRoadTrip.com have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. Camping Road Trip has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. Please be careful and responsible online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

While we strive to protect your information, Camping Road Trip cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information through the transmission process and you do so at your own risk.

Updating/deleting your Personal Information

You can request the individual information that Camping Road Trip, has collected about you, correct factual inaccuracies in your information, remove personal information from Camping Road Trip's databases and/or update your personal information here at My Account or please send an email to [administrator@campingroadtrip.com](mailto:administrator@campingroadtrip.com)

Use of your Personal Information

To "opt-in" means that you have notified Camping Road Trip that we have permission to collect and use your personal information to operate CampingRoadTrip.com and deliver the services you have requested. Camping Road Trip also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Camping Road Trip and its affiliates. Camping Road Trip may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. Of course, when we send you information on a new product for which you have "opted-in", you will be given the opportunity to "opt-out" of receiving such information in the future.

Camping Road Trip does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Camping Road Trip may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, birthday and name) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Camping Road Trip may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Camping Road Trip, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Camping Road Trip does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Camping Road Trip keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within CampingRoadTrip.com, in order to determine what Camping Road Trip services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within CampingRoadTrip.com to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Camping Road Trip will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Camping Road Trip or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Camping Road Trip; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of CampingRoadTrip.com, or the public.

Use of Cookies

CampingRoadTrip.com use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize CampingRoadTrip.com pages, or register with CampingRoadTrip.com site or services, a cookie helps CampingRoadTrip.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses. When you return to CampingRoadTrip.com, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the CampingRoadTrip.com features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of CampingRoadTrip.com.

Security of your Personal Information

Camping Road Trip secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Camping Road Trip secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Other Legal Notices

Any dispute over privacy is subject to this privacy statement and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages and application of the law of the State of New York.

If you have any concern about your privacy in connection with this policy, please send us a thorough description to [administrator@campingroadtrip.com](mailto:administrator@campingroadtrip.com), and we will try to resolve it.

We may post a revised privacy policy on our site. Please note that the use of information that we gather is subject to the privacy notice in effect at the time of use. You should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.
